[
  {
    "question": "Sustainability in the context of environmental sustainability is ____.",
    "options": [
      "multidimensional",
      "bidimensional",
      "unidimensional",
      "none of the given"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "As discussed by the Brundtland commission, sustainable development was the solution to the problems of ___.",
    "options": [
      "poor health",
      "recession",
      "poverty",
      "environmental degradation"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Environmental sustainability focuses on the impacts of processes, products and services on ___.",
    "options": [
      "biodiversity",
      "ocean environment",
      "air",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Social entrepreneurship is defined as solving social problems using ___.",
    "options": [
      "generational wealth",
      "market-based methods",
      "bank loans",
      "magical methods"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "HESI stands for.",
    "options": [
      "Health and Education Sustainability Initiative",
      "Higher Education Systematic Initiative",
      "Higher Education Sustainability Initiative",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Universal primary and secondary education is an outcome target of ___.",
    "options": [
      "SDG 1",
      "SDG 2",
      "SDG 3",
      "SDG 4"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "___ is a target group for ESD for 2030 framework.",
    "options": [
      "policymakers",
      "parents",
      "institutional leaders",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Successful implementation of ESD requires a shift in focus to ___.",
    "options": [
      "learning",
      "teaching",
      "exploiting",
      "reading"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "___ competency refers to the ability to reflect on one's own role in community and society.",
    "options": [
      "self-awareness",
      "emotional",
      "normative",
      "anticipatory"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2021, the European Centre for the Development of Vocational Training published a skills forecast scenario on the likely employment and skills implications of the ___.",
    "options": [
      "European Greenhouse Initiative",
      "European Green Deal",
      "European Green Agreement",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  }
]
